and this "marriage" will be over.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Zack:)I don't know if I want to sign it.
(Amy:)Ooh!
(Leonard:)Why won't you sign it?
(Zack:)I just think splitting up
can be rough on kids.
(Penny:)We don't have any kids.
(Zack:)Are you sure?
Because you didn't know
(Zack:)we were married
until this morning.
(Penny:)Okay, look, Zack, come on.
(Penny:)You know neither of us
thought this was real.
(Penny:)I mean, we were married
by an Elvis impersonator.
(Zack:)Of course it was an impersonator.
(Zack:)We could never afford
a real Elvis.
(Leonard:)You married him instead of me?
(Leonard:)Good call.
(Leonard:)Sign the papers.
(Penny:)Hang on.
You know what?
(Penny:)You have been a jerk
about this all day.
You always do this!
Whenever I mess up,
(Penny:)you're right there to make me
feel even worse about it.
(Leonard:)That is not true.
(Penny:)We could've waited till Monday,
(Penny:)signed the papers,
this all would have been over.
(Leonard:)You're the one who
invited him here.
(Penny:)There you go again.
Just another mistake
(Penny:)you're throwing in my face.
(Zack:)Not cool, bro.